{
    "subject": "resource/Th\u00e9ophile_Gautier",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1811-08-30",
    "human_readable": "Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was born on August 30, 1811.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.903536856174469,
            "question": "When was Th\u00e9ophile Gautier born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7769340872764587,
            "question": "What month was Th\u00e9ophile Gautier born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7282312512397766,
            "question": "In what year did Th\u00e9ophile Gautier's birth occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.653104841709137,
            "question": "What was Th\u00e9ophile Gautier's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.606229841709137,
            "question": "What is Th\u00e9ophile Gautier known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256562232971191,
            "question": "Was Th\u00e9ophile Gautier a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137335658073425,
            "question": "How is Th\u00e9ophile Gautier remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4330669939517975,
            "question": "What were some of Th\u00e9ophile Gautier's famous works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38128572702407837,
            "question": "What literary movement is Th\u00e9ophile Gautier associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3100292980670929,
            "question": "Did Th\u00e9ophile Gautier have a significant impact on French literature?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was born on August 30, 1811.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5094_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What literary movement is Th\u00e9ophile Gautier associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5094_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Th\u00e9ophile Gautier's famous works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5094_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Th\u00e9ophile Gautier remembered today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5094_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5094_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe triple \"Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was born on August 30, 1811\" is supported by the documents. The first document mentions a birthdate of 31 August 1811, but subsequent documents consistently state that Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was born on 30 August 1811."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Th\u00e9ophile Gautier was born on August 30, 1811, in multiple entries. For example:\n\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5094/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5094/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5094/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5094/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt\n- file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5094/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt\n\nThese documents consistently indicate his birth date as August 30, 1811."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}